https://www.tilia-inc.com/legal/privacy/

Tilia U.S. Consumer Privacy Notice
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully
to understand what we do with the personal information that you provide to us. This U.S.
Consumer Privacy Notice applies only to individual U.S. consumers and customers – persons
in the United States who use Tilia’s payment and stored value services. Persons located
outside of the United States are subject to our online Privacy Policy and not this Privacy Notice.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you utilize from us. This information may can include:
Name, Social Security number, date of birth, postal address, email address, phone number,
and any other information that we may use to contact you, verify your identity, or manage fraud
and other types of risk;
Payment and transaction information, including financial account information (for instance,
credit card and/or debit card account information, and payment provider account information;
Credit history and credit information that may be provided by identify verification sources to
help complete our identification process; and,
Username, password, secret questions, secret answers, and other types of authenticating
credentials to help verify your identity and the permissible use of our service or product.
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you utilize from us. This information may can include:
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
customers’ personal information; the reasons Tilia chooses to share; and whether you can limit
this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Tilia share?
Can you limit this sharing?
We do not share information for such purpose
Questions?
Call 1.855.979.1500 or go to www.tilia-inc.com.
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
Tilia Inc.
What we do
How does Tilia protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we maintain electronic, physical and procedural controls and safeguards, including but not limited to security measures that comply with applicable federal and state laws. We also require our service providers and business partners to whom we disclose the information to take similar measures.
Although we have implemented reasonable and appropriate safeguards to protect personal information, no security is perfect. We cannot guarantee that communications between you and us, or information stored on our websites or servers, will be completely free from unauthorized access or use.
To the fullest extent permitted by law, we disclaim all liability and responsibility for any damages (including but not limited to any and all direct, special, indirect, consequential or punitive loss or other damages of any kind, whether in contract, tort (including negligence) or otherwise, that you may suffer due to any loss, unauthorized access, misuse or alteration of any information we collect.
How does Tilia collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
Request products, services or information from us
Register an account with us
Participate in public forums or other activities on our sites and applications
Respond to customer inquiries or surveys
Visit or use our sites and applications or use our applications on third-party sites or platforms, including collection through technology such as cookies
Use your credit card, debit card or other payment method
We also collect information about you from others, such as individuals and financial institutions, credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies (such as identity verification services and consumer reporting agencies).
Please keep in mind that when you provide information to us on a third-party site or platform (for example, through our applications), the information you provide may be separately collected by the third-party site or platform. The information we collect is covered by this Privacy Policy and the information that the third-party site or platform collects is subject to the third-party site or platform’s privacy practices. Privacy choices you have made on the third-party site or platform will not apply to our use of the information we have collected directly through our applications.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Linden Research, Inc. (d/b/a Linden Lab)
Tilia Branch UK Ltd.
Non-affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. These entities can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Other important information
STATE PRIVACY LAWS
We will comply with applicable state privacy laws.
California Residents: We will not share your information with companies outside of Tilia, except for our everyday business purposes, for marketing our products and services to you, or with your consent.
Vermont Residents: We will not share your information with companies outside of Tilia, except for our everyday business purposes, for marketing our products and services to you, or with your consent.
We will not disclose credit information about you within or outside Tilia except as required or permitted by law.
Nevada Residents: Notice provided pursuant to state law.
To be placed on our internal Do Not Call List, call 1-855-979-1500.
If you would like more information about telemarketing practices, you may contact us at Tilia Inc., 945 Battery Street, San Francisco, CA 94111 or at 1-855-979-1500.
For more on this Nevada law, contact Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101; Phone number: 1-702-486-3132; E-mail: BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us.
DATA RETENTION
Tilia retains your personal information for as long as it is deemed necessary and relevant by Tilia for Tilia’s operations unless a longer or different retention period is required or permitted by law.
UPDATING, CORRECTING AND DELETING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
If your personal information changes or if you believe it is inaccurate, you may verify, correct or update it by contacting our Privacy Officer through any of the means identified above.
If you wish to remove your personal information from the Site, please contact our Privacy Officer in writing using the contact information found above with directions authorizing the removal of your personal information.
OTHER INFORMATION
See our online Privacy Policy to learn more about information collected through our website and how we use and disclose it. That Privacy Policy should be regarded as part of this Privacy Notice.
BUSINESS TRANSITIONS & ASSIGNMENT
Your personal information may be shared with or assigned to third parties in connection with Tilia undergoing a corporate reorganization, or negotiating or undergoing a merger, amalgamation with another entity or a sale of its assets, provided that the personal information so disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Notice by the entity acquiring the personal information. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against Tilia, such personal information may be considered an asset of Tilia and may be sold or transferred to third parties.
